(Kim Kang Min plays Choi Si Yeol)
(Park Jin Woo plays Na Aijun)
(Byung Hun as Yeon Joo Ha)
(Kim Hongjun plays Ji Kyusung)
("My idol is chasing me?!")
When did it start?
I wish our first kiss
can be vividly remembered in your mind
Was it when we kissed for the first time?
I always listen to your songs
The lyrics you write are kind of...
touching feeling
I got a lot of comfort
Or when he smiled and said he liked the song I wrote?
Or...
earlier
The day we spent the night together?
Are you... okay?
I think it should be from
From the moment I first saw you
From that moment on every day I
all the time
So cute
Everyone is looking for Luo Aijun
Let's just pretend it didn't happen.
Brother Aijun, wait a minute, listen to me...
I don't believe what you say anymore
And I never really liked you either
miss you so much
Luo Aijun I miss you so much
I really miss you
i from a long time ago
I like you very much
Although I haven't forgiven you yet
But…
I've liked you since a long time ago...
thank you
It doesn't matter if you don't need to forgive me. Really...
thank you very much
i like you
Brother Aijun
(Episode 10 Thank you for appearing in my world)
Ji Kuisheng
What are you doing?
I was so angry that I didn’t want to talk to you no matter what.
But I really can't help the anger in my heart
Even if I lie in bed, I can't fall asleep
you
come out with me
Come out now
What is this? What is this?
what do you want to say
How old is your new partner?
what
Didn't you say you have a new partner and want to break up with me?
Are you younger than me?
Yeah
He is about 25...years old
Yes, he is 25 years old
Show me the photo
what photo
Couples always take photos together
Show it to me quickly. Let me see if he is better looking than me.
photos
If not, then just video chat with him.
Call him quickly
Hello Lianzhu River
You are so anxious to find me
Is it just to say this?
enough
We'll be shooting next week
I don't have time to talk about this here.
I'll take you back
sit down
before i scream
ok
I've told you this before, right?
If you don't speak well and talk vaguely,
i will die
Hey, how can you say such things so easily?
Reporter Han Yanxiu is following me
what
He asked me if we had broken up and how could we break up?
Damn it, I obviously threw him away.
so
So how do you reply to him?
How
Are you afraid that I'll tell him that I'm still dating?
The important things are right in front of you now
If scandal blocks your future...
I thought
You really have a new partner
I thought you really abandoned me
-Isn't that the Lianzhu River? -Isn't that the Lianzhu River?
I never liked this about you
Think for yourself, decide for yourself
This time I was too angry and wanted to leave it alone.
But the more I think about it, the more I feel speechless
Sorry
I was wrong
The exam is finally over
Our classmates and teachers from Luoguang High School
Everyone has worked hard
Thank you for your hard work
Having said that
Teacher Luo, it’s such a pity
Even the trainee teacher experience only has three times left, right?
That is to say
You also have to return to your regular job. There is no other way.
So for the students who have finished the academic test,
I prepared a very awesome gift today
Then let's go give gifts together
It's really exciting
Diary of the last experience of "Go! Trainee Teacher"
Let's set off together now
CUT
Let's hit the board
(Ending scene of "Go! Trainee Teacher")
Let's change the scene
Good shot, good
Next…
Si Yeol's manager, please come over
good
I'll go over there
What's wrong
Can't we exchange these two days?
Didn't I tell you not to?
Today is the school anniversary. We must take photos on this day.
Why are you taking pictures during the school anniversary?
what
'You have to return to your regular job, there is no other way'
It's like we'll never see each other again
so sad
Didn't I say that?
I haven't forgiven you yet
Even if you haven't forgiven me
But you can still let me go
-It's pretty. -Isn't it? -Do you want to invite my sister to drink beer? -Yeah
-Oh, producer. -Please come over here.
-Please come over. -Okay.
Well...
-So handsome. -Please tell me your IG account
what
'Well...'
It means that his popularity has become too high, right?
so disturbing
thank you very much
You said you would shoot until the last episode
Although I didn't show it
You don't even know how happy I am
No
I'm sorry for you
No wonder everyone wants to avoid office romances
How many days are left?
I will try my best
Sorry to trouble you
By the way, have you considered my previous proposal?
You mean...
Amateur love reality program
-That's it... -Ah, that show
- And the last line has been changed. - Yeah.
When is the shooting time?
- What's the shooting time? I'll check again. - Okay.
I remember it seems to be next month
-Next month? -Yeah
Wasn't it just a holiday at that time?
Right
what
'How long is the filming period?'
wow
How can a character change overnight?
In short
Don’t even think about love shows in the future.
Did you hear that?
I want to see him cry again
What?
why don't you answer
OK
Anyway, I don’t like other people.
You're right next to me
Made me break into a cold sweat
No matter what you think
I seem to have become the super weak one
You think so too, right?
How
What are you laughing at?
No, although I have been chasing A-One for a long time
It seems like this is the first time I see you like this
I laugh when I think it's amazing
I also think I'm amazing
Although I'm a little embarrassed to say it myself
after i was born
Never pestered anyone else
But I'm done
I'm obsessed with you
All day long I have only you in my mind
This is a good phenomenon
keep it up
Oh
what is this
gift to you
That's the new peripheral product
Wow, I'm afraid this one will get worn out, so I'll keep it at home.
Oh my god, that's awesome.
You already have it
Take a closer look
You seem to like idol Choi Si Yeol more than me.
I seem to have heard this in my dream.
Alas
Not what you think
you see
Wow you can't even answer
are you jealous
This is you too
Oh…
So say
If you like me more
How can I love you more than I do now?
why not
I like you more every day
Otherwise, let's do this
Do you want to move into my house?
Moving?
What?
Did you order delivery?
Hello Choi Si Yeol
How are you two?
Ah, I'm so hungry
We're here to buy champagne
This is very expensive
- Come - Thank you
You also said you wouldn’t come after that day
what is this now
After our Shiyeol fell in love, we became an impenetrable wall.
I have to contact you first before coming back today.
Contact?
Who to contact
Aijun
'Ai...aijun'?
The two of them met outside and exchanged contact information.
But have you already entered into a relationship where you don’t use honorifics?
That's because we are the same age, so we immediately changed our words.
Because the reciprocal relationship was clear, we got to know each other super quickly.
Reciprocal...relationship?
This is super rare
I didn't win at that time, so I was very depressed.
thank you very much
Just speak up
But have you and Ji Kusheng been close friends since childhood?
Of course
I have photos of him from kindergarten. Can I show them to you?
Need I say more? Come on
you see
Wait
-Why was he so disobedient when he was a child? -Right?
So cute
Is this cute?
I also have photos of Choi Si Yeol when he was just waking up as a trainee
Is this okay for you to see?
Of course you want me to see it
Just wait, I'll find a few more
What are you doing? What's going on?
No
I thought he was a good person
I didn’t expect Zhuhe to be better than I thought.
I was originally wondering who Shi Yeol liked.
You have an excellent eye for seeing people.
Why are you doing this?
What the hell are you two doing?
Let’s not do this. Cheers, everyone.
Raise your glass quickly
You raise a glass too
The people I like are all here
Wait...
'people'?
Besides me, is there anyone you like here?
Our Shiyeol looks like this should be live broadcast and preserved
Even though it's annoying sometimes
But indispensable, my relative Ji Kyu-sung
And Ju Ha, a good friend whom I met because of Ji Kyu Sung
And I still can’t believe it
I have been chasing my fantasy for so many years
everyone gathers here
It’s really incredible. I’m happy and happy at the same time.
Yeah, very happy
-Cheers. -Cheers.
-Cheers -Cheers -Cheers
After finishing this bottle of champagne, is there anything else I can drink?
No. Back to your home
We don't have to leave until early in the morning
No. Why are you interrupting our date?
Are you not filming tomorrow?
No, I just came here because I didn’t have any filming.
Zhuhe
We are still in the early stages of our relationship
Life sometimes develops in unexpected directions
When did you two come?
- It's cold, right? - Yeah
give me your hand
After filming the movie, do we want to go on a trip?
Well…
where do you want to go
-Thank you for your hard work. -Thank you for your hard work.
See you on the day of the dinner
Let's go
good
To protect something
How much determination and consciousness do we need?
Are you hiring a teacher?
Yes, you will be a contracted teacher for another year this time.
Next time I will consider making you a regular employee
Just do it like now
Just teach quietly
You've always done a good job, Teacher Luo
right?
(Extension of contract for contracted teachers by 1 year)
in order to take responsibility
How many things do we need to give up?
OK I will try my best
(mom)
Aijun, you don’t need to give me any more pocket money.
My brothers and sisters are all grown up
I'm very grateful for what you've done so far.
i hope you can be happy
happiness
-Principal -Yeah
Sorry
I will only do it next semester
You...what did you say
I don't want to just stay here quietly
I will go where I can teach children and where I am needed more
Teacher Luo Aijun
To find what you desire
How long will we face the dark period?
No, Teacher Luo...
Will Si Yeol be busy in the second half of the year?
I wish I could give him a music show
Music program?
I didn't notice it before due to his appearance.
He is very good at making music
I'll let you know as soon as I confirm the itinerary
Preparation Start
Those things accumulated silently
What new turning point will it bring?
No one knows
Wow, that’s really great.
Wow, crazy
Came out...
This concept is really crazy
Wow, the agency is working hard.
Sometimes life is blessed by unexpected luck
Just like in the daily life that I thought was just boring and boring
My destiny is the same as the one who suddenly appeared one day
May the clear and warm rain
landing on everyone
Wow, today’s performance was awesome. I’ve watched it 10 times.
But will you come back immediately if you wear this?
Yeah
Because I missed you so much that I rushed back right after work.
When I get home, the people I love are there
So good
Stay home, the one I love is coming in
Luo Aijun
Should I take this opportunity to lock you in my house forever?
what
thank you for appearing in front of me
Thank you for appearing in my world
"My idol is chasing me?!" 》
Right
("Go! Trainee Teacher 2")
nice to see you again
Please give me some advice
"Go! Trainee Teacher" has been successfully scheduled to be broadcast
And Ben Ming, who is secretly in love with me
Still seducing me
Come, let's take a photo
-Okay -Okay -Okay, come on
We all come inside the camera
Hyun Ji bends down slightly
Minzhen and Junshu also came inside.
OK I want to shoot
1 2 3